{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Drywall Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40031/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40031,"taskName":"Drywall - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Drywall","xmTaskDescriptor":"Drywall Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":350,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"dry wall drywall, sheetrock, sheet rock, wallboard","textMessagingName":"Repr Drywall","rolloverLongDesc":"Repairs holes, cracks, water damage \u0026 other problems with existing wallboard.  For plaster on lath work, see separate category.","rolloverShortDesc":"Also called plasterboard, sheetrock \u0026 gypsum","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Drywall.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Drywall Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Ceiling \u0026 Drywall Hole Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":59,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex, or you have a variety of small projects, please ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"request a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Drywall Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Drywall - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Drywall Project","urlName":"Drywall-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Drywall Repair Contractors \u003cin_city\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"dry wall,drywall,ceiling,wall,sheetrock,hang,gypsum,board,wallboard,plasterboard,skim,coat,crack,patch","emcCategoryOid":-12025,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":355,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40031/":{"taskOID":40031,"originalTaskOID":40031,"setID":355,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":370,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which type of drywall damage needs repairing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4018,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Nails or screws popping","answerDisplayText":"Nails or screws popping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6145,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stress crack","answerDisplayText":"Stress crack","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4601,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patch small hole(s)","answerDisplayText":"Patch small hole(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4600,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patch larger hole(s)","answerDisplayText":"Patch larger hole(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5285,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Replace with new drywall","answerDisplayText":"Replace with new drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6852,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water damage in wall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Water damage in wall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6850,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water damage in ceiling(s)","answerDisplayText":"Water damage in ceiling(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6849,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Water damage around tub or shower","answerDisplayText":"Water damage around tub or shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":370,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which type of drywall damage needs repairing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4018,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Nails or screws popping","answerDisplayText":"Nails or screws popping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6145,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stress crack","answerDisplayText":"Stress crack","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4601,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patch small hole(s)","answerDisplayText":"Patch small hole(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4600,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patch larger hole(s)","answerDisplayText":"Patch larger hole(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5285,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Replace with new drywall","answerDisplayText":"Replace with new drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6852,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water damage in wall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Water damage in wall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6850,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water damage in ceiling(s)","answerDisplayText":"Water damage in ceiling(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6849,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Water damage around tub or shower","answerDisplayText":"Water damage around tub or shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4018,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Nails or screws popping","answerDisplayText":"Nails or screws popping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6145,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stress crack","answerDisplayText":"Stress crack","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4601,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patch small hole(s)","answerDisplayText":"Patch small hole(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4600,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patch larger hole(s)","answerDisplayText":"Patch larger hole(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5285,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Replace with new drywall","answerDisplayText":"Replace with new drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6852,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water damage in wall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Water damage in wall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6850,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water damage in ceiling(s)","answerDisplayText":"Water damage in ceiling(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6849,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Water damage around tub or shower","answerDisplayText":"Water damage around tub or shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}